<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Coleman R. Harris</title>
    <link>http://colemanrharris.me/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Coleman R. Harris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://colemanrharris.me/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Distance Matrix Anonymization Project</title>
      <link>http://colemanrharris.me/project/geo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://colemanrharris.me/project/geo/</guid>
      <description>I utilized the Lipschitz embedding method implemented by Kroll &amp;amp; Schnell in this paper to explore distance matrix anonymization myself. This included replicating some results from their paper, as well as applying it to a new dataset to explore its robustness when used alongside statistical analysis methods. Please explore the following analysis summaries if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more:
 Project poster (Presented at the Vanderbilt Data Science Institute Symposium, April 2019) Final report detailing analysis &amp;amp; results Analysis supplement  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oral Fluid Stability Study</title>
      <link>http://colemanrharris.me/project/aegis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://colemanrharris.me/project/aegis/</guid>
      <description>We organized a month-long stability study to observe over 40 different drug analytes of relevance and their associated stability in different temperature conditions.
The stability study is now used internally at Aegis Sciences to validate oral fluid forensic processes, and was designed as a benchmark the stability of drug analytes in the oral fluid matrix. One can find the associated presentation here, which I gave at the 2017 SERMACS conference in Charlotte, NC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Campaign Consulting</title>
      <link>http://colemanrharris.me/project/campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://colemanrharris.me/project/campaign/</guid>
      <description>Skills  Strong data &amp;amp; statistical analysis to support Field, Research, and Communications efforts Excellent communication skills to convey ideas to the team and to voters Adaptable programming experience to develop applications and models across the campaign Policy and research expertise to advise and craft candidates&amp;rsquo; policy positions Hard-working &amp;amp; fast learner to succeed in any campaign environment   Experience Data, Policy, and Research Consultant
Wade Munday for Tennessee Senate, TN - 25</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>